savemyrupee.com 2016-05-05

# SaveMyRupee.com | Latest Indian Deals, Coupon codes, Discounts, Offers and much more

_Privacy Policy_ What kind information do we collect?

We collect your personal information (like Email, name, city etc.) while registering in our site. Visitors have the flexibility to visit our website by not disclosing their email address. 

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in any of the following ways: 

  * To enhance & personalize your experience (your information would help us customize our contents according to your needs)
  * To send periodic emails on latest offers and coupons (The email address provided by you would be used to send periodic emails on latest offers, promotions, & coupons. It will be used to constantly communicate about our latest offerings and changes. We have provided the flexibility to opt out of our mailing list by unsubscribing from our mailing list. The unsubscribe link would be provided at the bottom of our emails)
  * To continuously improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. 

Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy 

Any changes to the current policy will get published on this page. 

www.SaveMyRupee.com
